littlecaprice.com 2019-09-19

# Privacy Policy ⋆ Little Caprice Porn

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from Little Caprice Dreams (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps

Third party analytics cookies – We use Google Analytics to help measure how users interact with our website content. These cookies “remember” what our users have done on previous pages and how they’ve interacted with the website. For more information on Google Analytics, visit [Google’s information page](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage). For instructions on how opt out of Google Analytics, see below.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address. We refer to this information as “Order Information.” We do not collect payment information, these data is collected by our Payment Provider Wirecard.

If you subscribe to our newsletter, we collect and store your mail address.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:  
Communicate with you;  
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and  
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

On some pages, you can purchase a Membership to littlecaprice-dreams.com, make requests, and register to receive access and materials. The type of personal information collected at these pages are name, age, email address, gender, etc.  
We use Wirecard and/or Epoch.com, who will obtain additional information such as your address and credit card data.  
The information collected by littlecaprice-dreams.com is used solely for the creation and maintenance of your Membership account. We do not sell, loan, lease, swap, trade or otherwise disclose your personal data. That information collected by Wirecard and/or Epoch.com is used for the purpose of processing payment of your Membership to littlecaprice-dreams.com.  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain it by logging on to the right user account pages, where the informations was collected. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information simply by modifying that information online.  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.  
You assures to have all rights for the submission of data and their publication to the system of littlecaprice-dreams.com. You agree to save harmless littlecaprice-dreams.com from all costs, which result from offences against it.

We also use your information (mail address, date of purchase/join) to remind you of discontinuing memberships.

We store the data you enter on the “do a scene” page solely for processing your application. We do not sell, loan, lease, swap, trade or otherwise disclose this data without a contract with you.

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Furthermore, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

DO NOT TRACK  
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.

DATA RETENTION  
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

MINORS  
The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18.

CHANGES  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US  
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at littlecapricedreams@gmail.com.
